(Sheldon:)And now that I think about it,
I stood in front of a case of iPods
(Sheldon:)and I bought a Zune.
(Amy:)What's a Zune?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, exactly.
(Sheldon:)It's an MP3 player
brought to us by the makers of Xbox.
(Amy:)No, what are you doing?
No, pick that back up.
(Amy:)You know it's good.
You did the research.
(Sheldon:)But what if I'm wrong?
(Amy:)You know what?
How about I buy it for you?
(Amy:)How about I buy you both?
(Sheldon:)You know I only have
one slot available
On my entertainment center.
(Amy:)Then I'll buy you
a new entertainment center.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, okay, sure.
But which one?
(Amy:)How about this?
I've heard that if you flip a coin,
(Amy:)it will tell you how
you actually feel.
(Amy:)Because you'll either
be disappointed
(Amy:)or excited by the outcome.
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Amy:)So, heads it's PS4,
tails it's Xbox One.
(Sheldon:)All right, I'll try.